pdf-word.net 2014-05-20

# Free eBook PDF File Download - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit PDF-WORD.net, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to any third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, the time you visited our site, the time you download pdf file on our list, and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Third Party Ads**

We use third party advertisements on PDF-WORD.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. Privacy Policy of Google is available at Google's [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Thank you for visiting our web site and enjoy your searching PDF Files from our list

## Latest PDF Files

### [CSharp Programming Tutorials](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Programming-CSharp/CSharp-Programming-Tutorials.html "CSharp Programming Tutorials")

#### category [Tutorial](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-pdf-files.html "CSharp Programming Tutorials") » [Tutorial Programming CSharp](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Programming-CSharp-pdf-p-1.html "CSharp Programming Tutorials")

Although CSharp is derived from the C programming language, it has features such as garbage collection that allow beginners to become proficient in CSharp more quickly than in C or C++ . Similar to Java, it is object-oriented, comes with an extensive class library, and supports exception handling, multiple types... more.

### [VB6 to VB Net Beginners Tutorial](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Programming-Visual-Basic/VB6-to-VB-Net-Beginners-Tutorial.html "VB6 to VB Net Beginners Tutorial")

#### category [Tutorial](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-pdf-files.html "VB6 to VB Net Beginners Tutorial") » [Tutorial Programming Visual Basic](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Programming-Visual-Basic-pdf-p-1.html "VB6 to VB Net Beginners Tutorial")

This tutorial is intended to show some of the differences VB.Net has introduced over VB6. This tutorial is aimed at the VB.Net beginner. It will show some of the major differences VB.Net has introduced over VB6. This tutorial does not cover changes in the IDE, only basic code changes. Table of... more.

### [Installing Ubuntu for Beginners](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Linux-Ubuntu/Installing-Ubuntu-for-Beginners.html "Installing Ubuntu for Beginners")

#### category [Tutorial](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-pdf-files.html "Installing Ubuntu for Beginners") » [Tutorial Linux Ubuntu](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Linux-Ubuntu-pdf-p-1.html "Installing Ubuntu for Beginners")

 Also, this one installation (which will take about 30 minutes), includes the operating sysytem, all drivers and all basic software. A typical windows installation will take about 45 mins, then about 15 minutes to load all the drivers, and then a further hour at least to load software (MS office,... more.

### [Introduction to Linux Command Line for Beginners](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Linux-Ubuntu/Introduction-to-Linux-Command-Line-for-Beginners.html "Introduction to Linux Command Line for Beginners")

#### category [Tutorial](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-pdf-files.html "Introduction to Linux Command Line for Beginners") » [Tutorial Linux Ubuntu](http://www.pdf-word.net/Tutorial-Linux-Ubuntu-pdf-p-1.html "Introduction to Linux Command Line for Beginners")

What you are installing on your computer is called a Linux distribution, or a Linux-based operating system. A Linux distribution takes all the parts mentioned above and assembles them, eventually polishing and customizing them. There are hundreds of good Linux distributions out there, and I couldn't contain all of them... more.

## Latest Shared eBook Entries

Share your ebooks and let others know you, your thought and your ideas through the ebooks. You can use our new feature to promote your ebook and get any comments, critics or recommendations about the ebooks. So **start promoting your ebook** and get your readers.

### [Home Construction Management Services](http://www.pdf-word.net/ebook/home-construction-management-services-3.html)

Bellamy Homes builders offering home construction management services

Author : bellamyhomes | Submitted Date : 28-03-2013 at 10:43   
Type : word | Pages : 1 | Size : 1.00 Mb | Like : 0 | Dislike : 0

### [php and sql](http://www.pdf-word.net/ebook/php-and-sql-2.html)

Php

Author : Alok Gupta | Submitted Date : 23-02-2013 at 08:44   
Type : pdf | Pages : 50 | Size : 10000.00 Mb | Like : 0 | Dislike : 0

### [Costume Jewelry In Casjewellery](http://www.pdf-word.net/ebook/costume-jewelry-in-casjewellery-1.html)

I have a costume jewelry pdf

Author : smoothlove | Submitted Date : 24-09-2012 at 04:24   
Type : pdf | Pages : 5 | Size : 0.40 Mb | Like : 0 | Dislike : 0

## Latest eBook Requests

You can now request a free/shareable ebook through our member area. This feature will let us or other members to find you the related ebooks and the results will be posted to your request page. We still work this in beta version and hope it can be fully available very soon. So **give it a try** and let others help you finding the requested ebooks.

## Latest Blogs

### [Insert PDF into Word](http://www.pdf-word.net/blog/insert-pdf-into-word.html)

Inserting pdf document into microsoft word document can be done in several ways and needs tricks to obtain better result for the requirements. Here are simple tricks used to insert pdf into word document without using any third party programs.

### [Choosing an eBook or a Printed Book](http://www.pdf-word.net/blog/choosing-an-ebook-or-a-printed-book.html)

There are considerations on choosing ebooks or printed books. This will be a critical beginning to enjoy reading articles, tutorials or references anywhere

## Latest eBook PDF File Views

## Latest PDF File Downloads

## Our Partners
